researchasahobby.com 2019-05-04

# ResearchAsaHobby.com Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy was last modified on the 14th of May 2018.

This Privacy Policy regards this website (“Site”, “our website”) which you can access at https://researchasahobby.com.

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site. 

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. 

**Information Collection And Use**  
While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (e.g. you specify your email when you leave your comments) or this is required as a technical part of website functionality (e.g. logs). Personally identifiable information may include your name, email, your website, cookies, logs (“Personal Information”). 

We do not collect or store any personal information that is not required for the proper functioning of our website.

We do not store your personal information longer than it’s needed for our website functionality.

If you want, you can [contact](https://researchasahobby.com/contact/) if you have any request which includes but is not limited to your personal data deletion.

**Email**  
We collect and store your email address if you subscribe to our newsletter. You can unsubscribe anytime by clicking the link provided in any newsletter email sent to you. 

We also collect and store your email address if you leave a comment on our website. We do it for informing you about the comment replies you get. If you are subscribed to the comment replies, you can unsubscribe any time by clicking the link provided in any notification email sent to you.

**Your name and website**  
We collect and store your name and the website which you specify when you leave your comments on our website. We do it for your convenience. Your name and website are displayed in the comments you leave so that other people (visitors of our website) could visit your website and call you by your name. 

**Log Data**  
Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. 

This information is collected automatically or in the special entry fields like on most other websites. We do not do it for your identification, but this is just how websites work. 

**Cookies**  
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive. 

Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site. 

For more information about cookies see our [Cookie Policy](https://researchasahobby.com/cookie-policy/).

**Security**  
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information using a professional hosting service and secure protocols of transferring data over Internet, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**  
We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. By visiting the Site you agree to this Privacy Policy.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](https://researchasahobby.com/contact/).
